I never thought Yuzuru
would just vanish like that...
At midnight, last night...
...the instant the date changed,
Yuzuru was erased.
Who is Natsumi impersonating
among the 12 people?
As long as I can't guess right,
will people disappear
every night, one by one?
That seems to be the case.
It'll get easier to guess
as the days pass, but...
...that means more people will be erased.
Tsk.
I've gotta find out who she is in a hurry.
Not only for everyone,
but for Natsumi, too.
In that case, Shido...
Isn't it about time you figure out
if I'm the real Kotori Itsuka?
You're the real one.
At the least, that's what I want to believe.
Is this any time to be saying that?
There's plenty of ways you could confirm it.
By asking me questions, or...
U-Um, in order to judge my reaction,
k-kiss me, or something...
I see...
In that case...
Eh?
Sh-Shido...
Hey! What are you doing, Big Brother!
Give it back! Give it back already!
--Yup! That's Kotori all right.
--Big Brother! Give it back! Give it back!
--There's no way Natsumi could
imitate this side of you...
--Big Brother! Give it back! Give it back!
...so well, right, Kotori?
U-Um, my dear Kotori?
I'd like to rush along
your dates with everyone.
"Episode Three:
'You're Natsumi'"
Right.
I know the schedule's
pretty tight as it is, but...
I want to fit as many people in
as possible before the day changes.
I'll leave the arrangements to you.
Understood. I'll do the best I can.
As for now, you can date Miku as planned.
Thanks.
H-Hey, Miku!
You never told me we'd be
going on a date in costumes!
Well, I'm kinda an idol, so...
It would be a pain if someone found out.
Don't worry.
You can cosplay freely in this park today.
Since we're finally on a date, I don't
want anyone to get in the way.
Well, I suppose that's true.
Wow!
It's Kanon Tsukishima and
Seig from Valkyrie Misty!
In the rare masks from episode
six when they saved Misty!
Can we please take your photo?!
Wh-What? No, we're...
Of course you can!
C'mon! You, too, Darling!
Wh-What?!
There it is! The signature
pose of our lovely Seig!
So?
What did you call us out for?
If you're making amends for
what you did, this isn't enough.
That's so lame.
No, this has nothing to do with that.
Since we're classmates, I thought
it's good to chat once in a while.
"Guidance Office"
Wh-What's the matter, Itsuka?
Wanting to talk about
the future all of a sudden...
Um, well. How do I put it...
I need to start thinking about
my future more seriously.
I see...
That promise you made me...
I haven't forgot about it either, Itsuka.
"Marriage Registration"
Eek!
Take this!
No way!
See that, Shido?
That was my special move,
Dunkelheit Windhose!
With my honed special move,
and this legendary item, the
Fegefeuer Gauntlet, in my possession,
you stand no chance to beat me, Shido!
Wait, legendary?
You just bought that over there.
Hmph! More importantly, lest you forget...
We promised the loser of our match
does whatever the winner desires.
I'm well aware.
Here comes my big comeback!
--Ah!
--Shido Itsuka falls apart!
You may sit.
R-Right...
My first order.
For the next ten minutes,
you won't be surprised, flustered,
or try to stop me, no matter what.
And you vow to never speak of it.
Eh?
A-All right.
I promise.
Good.
This is much more comfy than I thought.
You could even be my
full-time pillow if you wish.
Y-You little...
Do I hear the loser complaining?
Now then, shall I have
you pat my head, too?
As you wish.
Um, Kaguya?
Yuzuru... Yuzuru...
Kaguya, you...
You say there was an exam, but really,
you haven't found Yuzuru yet.
Of course I'd know. Don't think I'm stupid.
That's...
But, you thought it was better
I didn't know, right?
So, I'll believe...
Because that day, the one who
gave me and Yuzuru a third choice...
...was you, Shido.
Kaguya...
So, please...
Save Yuzuru... Save Yuzuru...
"Good grief, you're pathetic"...
...is not what I'll be saying today.
You beat the schedule and
dated 11 people in two days.
That'd exhaust anyone.
Well, I'm the one who asked for it.
So? Did you sense anything
wrong when meeting them?
Nothing in particular.
I think Miku and Kaguya have to be real.
My teacher and the girls
didn't seem off at all either.
It's hard...
I want to get it right quickly, but I don't
want anyone to be Natsumi either.
Yeah.
Even so, it's about that time
you need to give an answer.
I know.
But, even if want to guess who Natsumi is,
what am I supposed to do?
We don't really know that either.
This whole game goes along with
the whims and rules of Natsumi.
I imagine she's observing us
from somewhere at least.
Right on the money!
Kotori!
Natsumi!
Hi there, Shido!
Day two of the game is over.
Are you having fun yet?
What's this even about, Natsumi?!
I never asked for this game!
Just bring Yuzuru back and
I'll talk it out with you!
That's no good.
Even if you're not feeling up to it,
it's already set in motion, you see.
So, who am I impersonating?
I'm ready to hear your answer for today.
Th-That's...
Shido, someone will still get
erased if you don't answer.
Even a wild guess will do.
Tsk.
The one you're impersonating...
...is Yoshino!
I'm not confident, but...
She was that bold, so just maybe...
Hmm? I see.
Wait, Natsumi!
She's gone! Were you correct?
Shin, Kotori. Do you copy?
Reine? What's up?
Just now, again by Natsumi's Angel,
some people have disappeared.
Eh?
Both Ai Yamabuki and Yoshino.
It's two days later and I still
haven't guessed Natsumi correctly.
Ms. Okamine, Mai Hazakura...
Mii Fujibakama, and Tonomachi
have all been erased.
Shin, you're almost to the spot.
Sorry, did you wait long?
I just arrived.
I've been observing her, but...
She's been waiting here for over an hour.
"Dog & Cat"   "Terror"
"Galaxy"   "Love Story"
So, what are we watching?
I don't know. Haven't really decided.
In other words, you invited me
not to see a specific movie...
But because you wanted to go out with me.
Eh? Uh, well... I guess it's like that.
How far are we going?
As far as it goes.
Origami?
Wha--
I want you to touch me, too.
I'm not wearing anything today.
What? You...
That wore me out, heart and body...
Shido!
Tohka! Why are you out this late?
That's what I want to ask.
These past few days,
you've seemed so busy.
I'm worried about you.
Sorry.
Y-You don't have to apologize!
You're doing something
that you have to do, right?
Though, it's sad not being able to see you.
If there's anything I can do to help, say it!
Tohka... Thanks.
I feel like a new person now!
Oh! That's wonderful!
Yeah!
Hmm?
I'm sorry to bother you.
If I want to get to Tengu
Street, is it this way?
Uh, yeah.
Go left at the second light
and you'll run into it.
Thank you. My GPS is broke, you see.
I appreciate it, young couple.
Do you think I sounded awkward back there?
I doubt they suspect anything.
So that's Shido Itsuka...
...and Princess, huh?
Seems like they're doing well.
Well then, good night, Shido!
Natsumi!
Good night, Tohka!
Natsumi... "That I love you," was it?
I'm home, Kotori!
Shido! Where have you been?!
I heard from Reine just now!
--Eh?
--That Tohka...
That Tohka vanished!
Tohka! Tohka! Tohka!
Tohka!
Oh?
You seem a bit panicked today, Shido.
Natsumi!
It's not my fault.
You're the one who didn't come home.
So I took that as no guess for tonight.
Which means I erased
another person like usual.
You little...
Still, I'm thinking I wanna end this soon.
End this? Meaning what?!
If you guess correctly tonight, I'll return
all the people that disappeared.
But, if you don't guess right, it's my win.
I'll be taking the place of all your
missing friends from now on.
In other words...
Those 12 precious people will never
come back to this world again!
This time is special, so I'll
come back at 11:30 tonight!
Wait, Natsumi!
Natsumi!
I'll get it right.
I will... I'll save them.
Everyone...!
That Shido... He makes such a good
face when someone disappears.
But it's not nearly enough.
Show me what true despair looks like.
That's the fate of those who see my secret.
Let's see you drown in sorrow.
Nobody will be able to find me.
Because nobody looks for me anyways...
Yo...
It's been a while, Elliot.
Thirty years or so.
I see you're doing well, Ike.
That makes everyone then.
Shido...
I know it's sudden, but you all
know the situation now.
I got you all involved
in this... and I'm sorry.
Well don't fret about it.
But you should have told the truth
when Yuzuru disappeared at the start.
I'm a bit sad to hear our date was
all part of the search though.
I have lots of things to ask, but...
For now, I'll keep quiet and cooperate.
Thanks, everyone.
Let's go through it once more.
Natsumi is impersonating one
of these 12 people here.
So far, Shido has guessed...
...Yoshino, Ms. Okamine, and Mai Hazakura.
We can exclude these three.
And Natsumi has erased...
...Yuzuru, Ai Yamabuki, Hiroto Tonomachi,
Mii Fujibakama, and Tohka.
It's possible she was one of those five.
There's also the five of us here.
That makes us strong suspects,
but to impersonate one of us,
it would be hard for her to pull off.
Eh? What do you mean by that?
Yeah. Our traits are too complex
to be imitated by anyone.
Well, yeah... Something like that.
Witch... This Spirit you're
all calling Natsumi...
Why would she take such a risk?
The way she's does it,
every time a person disappears,
it raises the chance of guessing right.
By the end, it'll be hard to guess wrong.
Witch is confident she won't be guessed.
Meaning, no matter what
we come at her with,
we will never guess correctly.
For example...
She concealed herself as
a photo, or something.
True.
That's the sort of creative
thinking I think we'll need.
Do you think maybe she's
impersonating nobody at all?
I can't imagine that's the case.
Origami is right.
Natsumi is probably stretching the
rules to say safe the whole time.
Which means...
Could she be one of these five?
What a party.
Natsumi!
She's the one--
Oh, no! She's so gorgeous, it's no fair!
Thank you.
Now, it's the night we've been waiting for.
Shido, can you actually guess
who I'm impersonating tonight?
I'll get it all right.
Natsumi, for your sake, too.
Hmph. Give it your best shot.
Now, I'll give you three guesses tonight.
Each time you're wrong, one of your
friends right here will disappear!
C'mon, Shido.
Let's hear your first guess now. Go ahead.
Natsumi...
No matter how you look at it,
you can't be one of the four people here.
You wouldn't bet everything on
a game with a 75% chance to lose.
In other words, you're...
You're among the five people you erased.
You made yourself safe
as quick as possible...
...as someone we'd least expect.
And that's...
The first one who went, Yuzuru.
H-Hold on! Yuzuru was the real deal!
She did nothing I thought strange!
I know... I'm not certain either.
But...
If Natsumi was actually Yuzuru,
--everything makes--
--That's too bad.
You're wrong!
Origami!
Sh-She disappeared!
You're kidding! It wasn't Yuzuru?!
That's what I've been saying!
Come now, my great detectives.
Who will you name next?
If you run out of time,
I'll suck someone else up!
Elliot is on the move, too.
Let's fill the hole in
your support personnel.
The thing is, finding someone worthy
of an Adeptus number isn't easy.
But isn't there one?
The one who gave you that scar.
Now there's an outstanding Wizard.
Shit!
Calm down, Shido. I think
you're on the right track.
Who is Natsumi?! Who?!
Ah, jeez! I don't have any clue!
We just don't have enough hints!
Hey, time's almost up.
I can get rid of someone without
you guessing, but do you want that?
In that case, it's him!
Oh, too bad. That's wrong, too!
Kaguya!
Now, now. This is your last chance.
Who's going to be your final guess?
I can't take it, Darling! I can't!
To think I finally met Darling,
and now I'll disappear?!
Keep it together, Miku! Calm down!
Hey, hey. Thirty seconds left.
Tsk!
Please, Darling...
Take this.
I can't disappear without leaving
a piece of me with you!
Miku!
Because if I wear this,
it'll disappear together with me!
Wear this?
Together?
Eh? What are you doing, Shido?
I've got it, Natsumi.
That is, the reason you're so calm.
Hmm?
You're impersonating someone
in one of the 12 pictures,
but not one of the 12 people.
Natsumi is...
...right here!
Right, Yoshinon?
No way. Why would Yoshinon...?
Now that I remember, it was strange.
Yoshinon is Yoshino's puppet.
It shouldn't be able to see
something Yoshino can't.
What Miku said gave me the hint.
When Yoshino disappeared,
Yoshinon disappeared with her, too.
Well? How's that, Natsumi?!
Were you impersonating Yoshinon?!
You guys!
Tohka!
Shido! This is...
What happened to me?
Whew, I feel like I was
taking the longest nap...
Doubt. What am I doing here?
--Yuzuru! Yuzuru!
--Thank goodness, you're all okay!
Hey, Natsumi!
Why did you do all of this?
Time for you to explain.
Are you... Natsumi?!
Eh?
Eh?!
Haniel!
I see...
This is her form after
transforming with Spirit power.
You saw...!
You saw! You saw! You saw! You saw!
You've seen my secret, not once, but twice!
Unforgivable! It's unforgivable!
None of you are getting away with it!
Take this in place of farewell.
Just wait... I will have my revenge!
Wait, Natsumi! We can talk...!
Shido...
Eh?
They say there is only one truth, however...
The future ahead can be many, not one.
Which one do you choose?
Eh?!
"Episode Four:
'Transformation'"